Okay. I will admit that I missed the mark on the Jimmy Kimmel of it all. I missed the mark
because I was busy doing something and it kept being brought into my consciousness in a way
that was irritating. And so I missed the mark. And I will say this, I do believe that I'm being
goaded on this app. There has been a lot of people saying like, oh, we're getting your content again,
like you're not shadow banned anymore. And I do think that that is an effort to kind of like goat
me and put me into like in front of more people to try to entrap me. And I know people will be like,
you're a conspiracy theorist. You are correct. Because I've just seen way too many films that
prove that conspiracy theorists be actually right to ignore that. So I just saw something that was
posted on Variety that I want to read you. First, though, I want to, I just want to make a statement
real quick about, so this, just walk with me real quick. So what's going to happen is that the
government is going to be rendered basically, and I was saying this on, I was saying this when I was
on my radio show, the Amanda Seal show before Radio One flipped the script on me and, you know,
really showed themselves to be just the same old, same old black capitalists that don't give a fuck
about protecting anybody. I'll have that conversation another time. But I will say that I was always
saying on my show, you guys, you need to be conscious of the fact that this government is not going
to support you. So you need to make a point to consider what your needs will be. Because
your needs are going to be no longer met. Even if they're barely met, they're going to be no longer
met by this government. And I think that that was falling on deaf ears, unfortunately. But we are
here in, okay, so in case you missed it, you're an op. You're an op. When you're in protests, and there's
somebody that's goading y'all to get violent, I want you to know that you're an op. I want you to know
that they're an op. Okay? So I just want to, I want y'all to peep that. So we're in a chat and
there's someone in here that's saying, we need to burn shit down. We need to, we need to stop
marching. That's not how resistances start. They don't start by someone coming to random people
and telling them, oh, everybody needs to turn up. No, turn up happens by people who have signed up
to turn up because not everybody is cut the same way. So turn up is for particular people
that understand their role. It is not something that you yell in a crowd of everybody because turn
up also has to be done with strategy. So when you see people doing that, understand that they are an
op and call them out. When you're in protests and someone does that, everyone calls them out.
Everyone calls them out. Everyone calls them out. So when I see you in my app, in my comments doing
that, I'm going to call you out because you're an op because you're an op. Shut up CBS art box. No
resistance starts with education. I hate contrarians. They drive me fucking crazy. Um, as I was saying,
one of the things that's absolutely about to happen is please, someone define an op for this person
here. Um, an op is short for operative, not opportunist. Um, one of the things that is going
to happen though, is that you all need to really, really understand that the way that you exist,
the way that you consume is going to shift. Okay. It's going to shift. And so often people just
really don't see this until it lands in front of their face. And one of the things that's going to
shift is also how you in, how you interact with people, how you interact with people.
And I'm, I'm bringing this into a bigger conversation around like small business and, and, and, and
community, because we are so trained in this nation to, um, deal with, um, only like big box business
that we are really, um, we have been convinced. We, we have actually been convinced that, um,
um, that we, that like our money gives us the right to punish. Our money gives us the right to
be rude, et cetera. We do this all the time. Like I know when I was doing standup, when people would
come to my show, like there would be people that like felt some type of way about what I was saying
and then would be like heckling. And then when I would require to, when I, when, when I know opposition
op is short for operative y'all, it's not short for opposition. It's short for operative. So the,
but, but then they're heckling and they'd be like, well, I paid so I can say what I want. Yeah.
That's not how it works. But what we have been, we have been absolutely trained in this nation
to think that, um, we are all authorities. We, we, we literally have been trained to try to be
authoritarian in our own situations. I say that to say that when you are making this transition,
you're going to have to undo that because y'all are so used to dealing with nameless, faceless
interactions that you don't know how to interact with actual people. And actually for what it's
worth, that's on both sides. That's on both sides because these big companies hire these massive
amounts of people to just sign, to just answer the phone and they do not know how to actually
listen to people. They're reading a script. English might be their fourth language. And so there's no
like connection. And so we don't know how to actually do customer service because we don't even know how
to do human interaction. So like a lot of times I will be on both sides of this on one side as a
customer. I'm just like, why are you not listening to what I'm saying? And it's because they have been
trained only to think in the sense of, um, risk assessment. They're only trained to think about
how do I not have to make the company pay to replace this thing? And so they put you through
all types of nonsense. They put you through all types of back and forth. Well, we'll give you a 20%
discount. Give me a fucking refund because I bought a waterproof blanket from you. That is not
waterproof. Why do I have to go through a 20%, 40%, 60%? Like this is this, right? And yes,
to what Kishon is saying, I'm about to expound upon that too. Like people don't want to do a,
don't want to, uh, even interact with people anymore. I know a brother who is literally setting
up his whole business to operate with AI as the interactions because people are like, people treat
him different when they realize he's a brother. So anyways, as me on my other side, as a, as a owner
of a business, the amount of people that will be like, I didn't get my shit. You need to pay me a
refund immediately. You know? And it's like, it's done as a punishment. You need to recap. You need to
send me a meat. It's a punishment. And we, that's how we interact with people. That's how we deal with
people in punishment. We are in a scenario right now where you got folks who are pretending to be
a moral authority, trying to literally punish people for not responding the way they want them
to. And I want you to know that what we are seeing is actual suppression of the highest order.
And I missed the mark when the, um, I missed the mark when the, when the Charlie Kirk news came out
because I was busy doing my own shit and, um, it was much deeper than what I originally assessed.
It was much deeper than what I originally assessed because basically this Charlie Kirk thing is being
used as the next turning point. Um, it, that was interesting. That was, that was quite punny. Um,
in their, uh, in their movement. So today, um, Variety puts out that the
Jimmy Kimmel live show will be replaced tomorrow by a CK tribute special on Sinclair's ABC affiliate
stations. The company is demanding Kimmel apologize to Kay's family and send a meaningful personal
donation to them and turning point USA, the organization that dude founded that advocates for
conservative politics in high schools and colleges. Mr. Kimmel's remarks were inappropriate and deeply
insensitive at a critical moment for our country. Sinclair's vice chairman, Jason Smith said in a
statement, we believe broadcasters have a responsibility to educate and elevate respectful,
constructive dialogue in our communities. We appreciate FCC chairman Carr's remarks today.
And this incident highlights the critical need for the FCC to take immediate regulatory action to
address control held over local broadcasters by the big national networks. Um, I can't say this
enough. We will not be here on this Instagram for much longer. Also breaking is that the TikTok US deal
has been finalized and the app will now have its own separate Zionist algorithm. Uh, Oracle,
which is owned by an Israeli CEO, who was a Jewish Zionist man, um, Silver Lake, which is a Zionist
organization and Andreessen Horowitz, who is a Jewish Zionist founder will now control the US TikTok.
There will be an American and Israeli board with US and Israeli government oversight. US users will
download a new app that looks identical to current TikTok, but runs entirely on US Israeli controlled
algorithms. We're just giving you a second to soak that up. So remember when I was yelling about
Kamala Harris needing to align with people who are against the genocide and remember how the Democrat
Democrats in the past few months have refused to align with any socialists or anyone who is supporting
Palestine. Remember how many of us have been yelling for the past two years, yelling for the past two years
about Israel and y'all said, that's over there. That has nothing to do with us. Do you remember that?
You know, Kanye was, was, was, was so annoying because he actually could have been effective
if he wasn't actually anti-Semitic because anti-Zionist would have been supported, but instead he
showed that he actually is anti-Semitic, which is not what we're about. And so I want you also to,
instead of asking people, what should we do? What should we do? What should we do? I want you all
to instead be making suggestions and stop acting like you can't think for yourself. So here's a whole
comment section of people. And I'm asking you, what should we do? Because like folks can't even figure
out where to spend their money or how to not be stank, you know? So when I say, what should we do?
I'm not talking about like TikTok. I'm talking about like living. There you go, Lili403. Shireen,
I'm not against upscrolled at all. I just don't know anything about it yet. There you go, Noel.
Well, there you go, the fat man. You the right mofo for that one. So there's a book by NMK Jemsen
called The Fifth Gate. And in it, she, um, one second. And in it, she, um, she, she envisions like
life would be on like a planet, you know, similar to earth, you know, in, in like a future, but she
talks about communities that basically find their safety behind, you know, walls and everyone has a
particular role in this, in this community. And I think that, you know, you guys are going to need
to really ask yourselves, what role are you in your community? Cause I don't think, you know,
we're not even taught to know because we're really only taught to, um, to serve the empire.
You feel me? Read the comments. People are saying really good stuff in the comments.
Thank you, Zoa. Read the comments. You got community right here. And then maybe you don't,
maybe, maybe you aren't the thing that you want to be in your community. So then maybe it's
finding who that person already is and connecting with them and, um, you know,
apprenticing, so to speak. You know, I thought that I was supposed to go get my PhD
and, um, I thought I was supposed to go get my PhD. And so I started the process and I,
I was committed to the process and, and then I went to the school. I was only applying to one
school and I went to one information session at the school and there were two professors that were
speaking. And one of them was talking about poets, like spoken word poets, like her work is about
spoken word poets of the last 20 years, black women, spoken word poets of the last 20 years.
Do I think that I'm going to answer that question. Someone asked, do I think we can actually win
this fight? I don't think y'all even know what the fight is. Y'all can't identify enemies or heroes.
This, this country, you know, is, is, has been very effective at, at, at, um, teaching people how to be
dummies. Um, and we got to make it our business to be like, I don't want to be a dummy. Nonetheless,
as I was saying, um, I realized that I wasn't supposed to be there
because the knowledge that they were providing, I already have. So I need to get new knowledge
and, um, I need to, that, that's where my PhD is. I need to get knowledge that is outside of an
institution, the knowledge of the earth, indigenous knowledge. I need to get wisdom. I don't know,
Dala, why are you on this live? Get the fuck on if that's how you feel. As I was saying, do I think
that, um, we can win this fight? No. Also like, what are you trying to win? Do you even know what,
what, what, what you're trying to win? Freedom. What does freedom look like? Thank you, dance for
everyone. That means a lot. What does freedom look like? Peace and prosperity. Um, freedom is agency
creating spaces for us by us. Freedom means being untethered to be liberated. All of this is just
like fancy words, like really like, um, high vibrational, like that kind of language, but it's not
like practical. Like what is freedom? You are reading memes. I feel like you're reading posters
that you get the Scholastic Book Fair. I'll tell you what my version of freedom is. My version of
freedom is knowing that as a part of a community, I am enriched and protected by that community
while also holding responsibility and obligation to that community. I think a lot of people's version
of freedom is, is not having responsibility and not having obligation. Their version of freedom is
individualism, is being able to do whatever you want to do without having any, without having to come
to the table, without having to, um, you know, actually care about others. What we're witnessing is
these are those people's version of freedom. Some people's version of freedom is the oppression of
others. They want to be free to oppress others. They want to, they want to be told what to do because
they want to be free from having to think. Some people's version of freedom is literally being a
drone. Some people's version of freedom is being allowed to live in their shadows, being allowed to be
the personification of their trauma and, and to be someone else's trauma without conscience.
That's the world that the United States is. I mean, it has acted that way in other places,
but on its own soil, it has not existed in such a fashion. However, that is where this world is now.
The United States is that it is a freedom of shadow and, um, unfettered hatred, bolstered by violence.
Like that's, that's their, they want to be free to hate. That's some people's version of freedom. So,
so when we say the word freedom or we say, you know, we need to be liberated, like you got to really
know what that means. What are you actually fighting for? What are you actually trying to
make happen physically and mentally? Because a lot of us are really actually sleepwalking,
you know? We're really just like, I got to get this check. I got to feed my kids. I got to da,
da, da, da, da. And, um, that's by design. However, many of us are doing that by choice,
you know? So when we talk about liberation, I just think that for some of y'all, you think
liberation, liberation is like a fancy word for freedom. It's like the high, it's like the high,
like the high vibrational word for freedom. Thank you, Ofa. Hi, Tunisia. And it's, it's,
it's really not. And you don't really start to understand what liberation is until you,
until you truly start to understand the globe, until you start to understand the history of the
world. So you can't even, many of you can't even consider your own version of liberation because
you don't have a context to even pull from of true oppression. So, uh, yeah, that's, you know,
that's, that's, that's what we own. And, um, and it's like, I'm trying to, I'm trying to like
encourage people to, to wake up out of the sleepwalking state and see that, um, they,
you all have to be much clearer. You have to learn language. Like, like, you know, I see some people
in here saying like, I'm learning different languages. And I think that is incredible.
I will also say that a lot of folks don't even know English, you know, how to speak English,
but you don't know how to communicate. You feel me? I'm gonna say that one more time. You know how
to speak English, but you don't know how to communicate because you got to learn how to
communicate your feelings, how to communicate your thoughts, you know? And a lot of folks don't have
that. They don't have that capability. And so these are the things that we have to be really
actively working to, to understand if we're really actively working to, um, be obstacles
to these folks. They don't think highly of you. They think you're incapable. I think that's a version
of freedom, but I don't think that's just freedom because some people's possessions mean a lot to
them. I don't think that that possessions doesn't house have to be material. There's no, I just really
wish y'all would, would, would realize that like you're, you're like the, like the same people who
will be like, how are we going to win are not demanding anything of the people who were asking you
to vote for them? Like that, that, that, like it's those types of contradictions that, that really
like get me annoyed. Like it doesn't even bother folks that Kamala Harris is on a book tour while
fascism is descending upon us because they say, you know, she, she did her job as, as, as if she,
what job. So, you know, I just like, I don't know. I, I, I don't know. I have a lot of thoughts today,
but I, okay. So the reason why I said that is because anyone who is not against what is harming
you is for it. Anyone who is not, the fact that you all look at being the president as a career
is like, like that's bug to me. You know what, Mark, Mark, check your texts. I was, um,
listening to Orientalism and I had a whole stream of consciousness in your texts. Anywho,
I feel the study to just say, y'all niggas is racist. What that book is about. Y'all niggas is
racist. Everything you've been saying about us is because y'all niggas is racist. That was the most
eloquent expression of y'all niggas is racist. Anywho, um, y'all like, I'm not done with Orientalism,
but like, that's essentially what the book is. Y'all niggas is racist. Stop talking about us.
Edward Saeed, stop talking about us. That's essentially what he's saying. Stop talking about
us. Cause, cause y'all can't talk about shit without being racist. So just stop. Let, let us
talk about us unless you're going to attempt, unless you're going to talk about us without
your racism. Why do y'all ask me these dumb questions? Why would I run for office? I think
y'all do it to annoy me. Don't talk about us cause y'all's racist. That is what Orientalism is about.
I mean, it's of course much deeper than that, but that's the, that's the top line.
Y'all, y'all don't know how to talk about shit without being racist. So don't talk about it.
And if you say Delta University one more time, I'm going to block you. Cause I'm just going to
assume you're a bot. I'm not going to do a Kamala parody and do a book tour. I'm going to do a book
tour with a book that actually enriches people. Melania, I've been talking about it and you don't get
to control what the hell I'm talking about right here. I've been talking about it. Talked about it
every goddamn day. Talked about it yesterday. I talked about it the day before. I talked about it
last night. Like I don't, I just, you know, cut it out. Book is full of BS. Kamala's full of BS.
I'm going to end by saying this though. And I'm just going to say this about myself.
Um, first of all, thank you. You see me putting together orders. So thank you to everybody who
supports, you know, the work I do, because this is the work that supports me. You know, I don't,
I don't get speaking engagements at colleges anymore. I don't get, um, I, you know, I left
Hollywood. I'm not aspiring to be in films and TV. I'm an incredible actress and I have a, I have a
resume. Like I absolutely could have decided to do that. And I chose not to. Um, and you know,
I bought my book back from Simon and Schuster and I, I'm not saying this as like, woe is me,
but I am saying this as, you know, there has to be patronage for those who are giving, right? For
those who are giving all the time. And sometimes that patronage shows up in dollars. Sometimes that
patronage shows up by showing up. So for instance, when I do free shows, when I do create free content
and people show up, what's up guru? Um, that is patronage, right? Like that is also
showing up. And it's, it's like, I think a lot of people are so under the, the, the spell of
capitalism that they forget that they forget that you can also support with your body, even if you
don't got bread. So, you know, sometimes you can, you can actually just show up to some shit and be
a body in the room and a brain in the room that's assisting. And that is also valuable. Now, when I'm
doing my stuff and I'm, I'm selling myself and I'm pushing myself and, and, and, and people don't
realize like I'm a merchant, you know, I'm a merchant and everything that you see me pushing
is coming from me. It's not coming. There's, there's no sponsors. There's no investors. It's
coming from, from me to you with the goal of inspiring you with the goal of encouraging
you with the goal of empowering you. And so, um, you know, I think it's, it's something
that we're going to have to really like re re recalibrate our minds to understand why
we support things, why we give our money to things. Right. Um, because people are giving
their money to things. When you give your money to Walmart, it's because you're getting
something you want. And so, yeah, you need to be on them. But when you give your money
to an independent person, who's like making their products, you need to really think about
why you're giving them their money and you need to interact with them in, in kind, because
that is how the world is about to become for you. We are not going to be in a big box world
much longer where we, we, we, the United States has overextended itself and it's going
to crumble and you're going to need to rely on how you interact with your mom and pop
and individuals. And, and, and that is something that people have lost practice with. Um, you
know, and it's not to say that you shouldn't expect, you know, to get what you've paid for.
You shouldn't expect to get what you've paid for. Absolutely. Um, but we have to re we, I
do believe that we need to recalibrate our sensibilities because I think that we absolutely have
been, um, like we've just been trained in a, in a bad way. So anyways, I'm going to go
because I have so much work to do in terms of getting these orders out and getting, making
sure people are happy. Thankfully, I have some help coming over today to help me organize
things. And, um, I have the Amanda Land Summit this weekend, which I haven't even been able
to prepare for. Uh, thankfully I have help that is actually doing all the behind the scenes
stuff so that I'm not just there by myself. So looking forward to, to that. And, um, you
know, let's, uh, let's keep cracking.